We're actually partnering with IBM to build
在本次课程里
this really great project for everyone to utilize in the classroom.
我们还跟 IBM 合作创建了一个非常精彩的项目
Can you give us a little insight into the platform that they'll be
你能给我们介绍一下项目中使用到的平台
using and the data that they'll be getting out of it.
以及平台里的数据吗？
Right. Yeah. So, the project is cool.
好的 这真的是一个很酷的项目
I like the project.
我个人非常喜欢
I thought it was a great idea when we got started working on it. What is the project?
我们最初开始创建这个项目的时候 我就觉得这个想法特别棒 什么样的项目呢？
Well, on Watson Studio, an important component,
在我们的 Watson Studio 里
as we discussed, is the community.
有一个很重要的部分 就是它的社群
The community is collaborative ecosystem of curated datasets, articles, notebooks.
是一个包含很多精选数据集 文章以及 notebook 的协作型生态系统
Other kinds of assets that are out there in the world of Data Science,
还有很多跟数据科学
Machine Learning, and artificial intelligence.
机器学习 还有 人工智能有关的资源
Our users on the platform interact with these assets.
我们的平台用户会和这些资源互动
So, what the students are building and what we've built,
所以 我们要和同学们一起构建的
is a recommendation system for these assets in the community.
是社群里的一个推荐这些资源的推荐系统
One thing is that what we do is,
我们主要负责的是
we go out there ourselves and we curate also with models that we develop here at IBM.
用我们 IBM 的模型来精选内容
All these assets that are out there.
从所有的资源里面
What students will be doing is building in that part where it makes it personal for
然后学员做的是个性化推荐内容
an individual user and providing
使它们能够符合用户的个性化需求
that personalized recommendation experience with a Web App.
并用一个网络应用来实现个性化推荐
So, it sounds like this is actually something that isn't on your platform,
所以 这听上去像是一个目前你们的平台目前还不具备
but could be really useful to people on your platform.
但会对平台的用户很有帮助的东西
Yeah. That's right.
是的 对的
Now that's very cool. Students will be working on a recommendation system
太酷了 学员们会构建一个为我们社群用户
to personalize recommendations for people who are already in the community.
推荐个性化内容的推荐系统
That's right. Yes. So, the data that they'll have is
没错 所以 他们拿到的数据
anonymized data of the interactions
都是存在于社群里面、
between all of the different kinds of articles and datasets,
匿名的、
and that sort of thing we have in the community, and our users.
包含各种文章和数据集之间互动的数据
So there's that communication between what they're actually doing on the platform
它们能揭示用户们在这个平台上在做什么
interacting with those assets and all of that is actually
如何与各种资源进行互动
part of the data that they'll take advantage of.
这就是学员们会用到的数据
So, that's pretty exciting,.
听起来很棒
I think. Yeah, sounds like a really cool project.
是的 听起来是个很棒的项目
Yeah.
同意
It also sounds like,
也就是说
students will be able to tackle this recommendation system.
学员会跟推荐系统打交道
However, they might want to which could be like looking a how users are connected,
但同时 他们还需要去发现用户间的联系
how articles are connected,
文章之间的关系
how different types of media are connected.
以及不同的媒体资源之间又怎么互动的
That's right.
是的
There's like lots of different ways that they could go about creating a solution.
听上去可以有多种创意解决方案
Very cool.
好酷